那么你是如何把UI分割成一个一个的小块的呢？
So how did you break up the UI into smaller components?
你可能认为这里是两列，
Well, you might have thought that this could be two columns, but
但是这里的元素却是很难定位的。
then it would be hard to position the elements here. You
你从屏幕高度看它是垂直居中的，
could center them vertically within the height of the screen, but it
但它却不一定与左侧的温度视图对齐。
wouldn't necessarily line up with the temperature views on the left-hand
反而，这更像水平线性布局结构。
side. Instead, this looks more like a horizontal linear layout. Then, the
而其他部分的元素可以使用垂直线性布局。
rest of the elements could be laid out by using a vertical
垂直线性布局将有6个子元素。
linear layout. The vertical linear layout would have six children. The third
第三个元素还采用了水平线性布局，并包括两个子元素。
element would be a horizontal linear layout, composed of two children.
这两个元素，一个是由两个文本视图垂直组成的，
The first would be another vertical linear layout with these two texts
一个则是由另外两个垂直视图组成的。
views, and the second element would be another vertical linear layout
为了屏幕内容能够垂直滚动，
composed of these two 2 elements. To make the contents of the
我将这些元素都放入scroll view中。
screen vertically scrollable, we put it inside a scroll view. Using
这里我们用列表视图就会显得浪费，因为我们不需要将列表项扩展到无限条，
a list view here would be overkill, because we don't need to
我们也不会再次使用这些列表项。
scale to an infinite number of item and we don't need recycling.
这有在屏幕上显示的确定数字，所以scroll view是更好的选择。
There's a fixed number of fields on the screen, so a scroll
我将向你展示实现这些元素的具体XML布局代码。
view is the perfect choice. I can show you our implementation for
我们将一些数据固定编码在layout，
the fragment detail XML layout. We hard coded some data in the
这样就能在设计面板上预览了。
layout, so that it would show up as a preview in the
这里我们可以看见根节点是Scroll View。
Design Pane. At the root of the View hierarchy, we have a Scroll
Scroll Views最多只能有一个子项。
View. Scroll Views can only have max one child. So we set
所以我们将之设为垂直线性布局。在这个布局中，
that to be the vertical linear layout. Inside of this layout, we have
我们有文本视图显示一周中的一天，日历日期，
a text view for the day of the week, the calendar date,
然后是一个水平线性布局的。随后是湿度文本视图，
and then a horizontal linear layout. This is followed by the humidity text
风力文本视图和气压文本视图。
view, wind text view and pressure text view. In the XML
在XML代码中，我们看到scroll view中包含了预览用的线性布局。
code, we see the scroll view with the trial linear layout. We
我们使它的padding为16dp，
give it some padding of 16dp, so that the content does
这样内容就不会冲靠在屏幕边缘。
not flush up against the edge of the screen. Then we see
然后我们看到文本视图，接着是水平线性布局。
the text views followed by the horizontal linear layout. We specify
我们指定layout margin top为16dp，让文本视图的底部有更多空间。
layout margin top of 16dp to give it some more space from
在这个水平线性布局中，
the bottom of this text view. Within this horizontal linear layout, we
我们有一个垂直线性布局，它的width为0 weight为1。
have one vertical linear layout which has a width of zero and
另一个线性布局也是这样，
a weight of one. And another linear layout with the
width为0 weight为1 。
width at zero and a weight of one. That means that
意思是这两个子项具有相同的宽度。
both of these children have equal width. For this linear layout,
对于这个线性布局，我们让gravity为center_horizontal。
we specified gravity to be center horizontal. That means that the
意味着，在这个布局中，内容将被水平居中放置，包括图标
contents inside of it will be centered horizontally, which includes
以及预报文本的视图。
the icon, as well as the forecast text view. Lastly, we
最后，我们将剩余的文本视图用来显示其他的天气情况。
have the remaining text views for the other weather details. When
当我们更新更详细的内容时，布局会看起来更好一点。
the layout looks good, we update the detail fragment. At this
这个时候，我们可以将其移动到自己的文件中。
point, we also move it into its own file. In the
在onLoadFinish方法中，我们曾用大量的findViewById调用。
onload finish method, we used to have a lot of find view
然而，我们我们可以更早的缓存住他们，这样就只要查找一次。
by ID calls. However, we can cache those views earlier so that
在onCreateView方法中，
we only have to fetch them once. In the onCreateView method, once
一旦视图被解析，我们就可以
the view is inflated, we can go and find a reference
找到所有后续要使用的视图的引用。
to all the views we'll need later. We store these views as
我们把这些视图作为类的成员变量来保存。
member variables in a class. Which is why they start with the
所以他们都以m开头。在onCreateLoaded方法中，
letter M. In the onCreateLoaded method, we make sure that the projection
我们确保从内容提供器中查询的映射包含了所有我们需要的信息。
that we're requesting from the content provider contains all the information
特别是，我们刚刚为止添加了视图的那几个新的字段。
that we need. Especially the new fields that we just added views
然后在onLoadFinish方法中，
for. Then in the onload Finish method, we get the cursor
我们用游标返回我们需要的信息。我们通过游标读取天气情况ID。
back with the data we need. We read the weather condition ID
我们以后将会用到这个来确定正确的图标。
from the cursor. And we're going to need this later to determine
但现在，我们可以先用一个占位图标。
the right icon. But for now, we can just use a placeholder
我们继续从游标中读取数据更新视图，
icon. We continue reading from the cursor and updating the views such
比如日期、简介和温度。
as for the date and description and temperatures. For the new views
对于湿度、风力、气压这些新视图，
for humidity, wind, and pressure, we read the
我们读取光标位置的信息，然后正确的为UI格式化信息。
information from the cursor, and then we format it
这就涉及从代码片段中拷贝
properly for the UI. This involved copying over
字符串和工具方法了。
the strings and the utility method from the gist.